Ningninghou: It's like this. Let's Start Deduction Tongcheng Travel
Ningninghou: Let's survey the area first. Let's Start Deduction Tongcheng Travel
Ningninghou: Nan, you take this area, okay? Let's Start Deduction Tongcheng Travel
Nan Nandu: Okay. Let's Start Deduction Tongcheng Travel
Jin Jinliang: I'll take that area. Let's Start Deduction Tongcheng Travel
Ke Ke'ai: Okay. Tongcheng Travel
Tongcheng Travel
Ningninghou: You take that area. Let's Start Deduction
Ningninghou: How about you? Tongcheng Travel
Ke Ke'ai: I'll search by the dining table. Tongcheng Travel
He Heda: I'll take this area. Let's Start Deduction Tongcheng Travel
Ningninghou: This area. Let's Start Deduction Tongcheng Travel
Tongcheng Travel
Nan Nandu: There's one under here too, remember that. Let's Start Deduction
Nan Nandu: Take a look. Let's Start Deduction Tongcheng Travel
He Heda: Okay. Let's Start Deduction Tongcheng Travel
Tongcheng Travel
Countdown begins.
Ningninghou: Check that out too. Let's Start Deduction Tongcheng Travel
Dingdingdang: There's something under this table. Let's Start Deduction Tongcheng Travel
Li Liwo: There's a sound. Let's Start Deduction Tongcheng Travel
Li Liwo: Intruder! Let's Start Deduction Tongcheng Travel
Li Liwo: Someone's over there. Let's Start Deduction Tongcheng Travel
Nan Nandu: Where did he come from? Let's Start Deduction Tongcheng Travel
Tongcheng Travel
Nan Nandu: Don't touch me! Let's Start Deduction
Li Liwo: Someone's here. Let's Start Deduction Tongcheng Travel
30 seconds deducted. Let's Start Deduction Tongcheng Travel
He Heda: You just wait. Let's Start Deduction Tongcheng Travel
Li Liwo: What? Let's Start Deduction Tongcheng Travel
Li Liwo: Who's there? Let's Start Deduction Tongcheng Travel
Li Liwo: Who? Tongcheng Travel
Li Liwo: What is this? Let's Start Deduction Tongcheng Travel
Li Liwo: What is it? Tongcheng Travel
Li Liwo: What is it? Let's Start Deduction Tongcheng Travel
Li Liwo: What? Let's Start Deduction Tongcheng Travel
Li Liwo: It's not human! Let's Start Deduction Tongcheng Travel
Li Liwo: It's not human!
Li Liwo: What else?
Li Liwo: What else is there?
Ah!
Li Liwo: Who is this?
30 seconds deducted.
Oh my god!
Li Liwo: It's over.
Li Liwo: This room is full of people.
Ah!
Li Liwo: So scary.
Dingdingdang: Let's just be bold this once.
Dingdingdang: We're definitely failing this time anyway.
30 seconds deducted.
Dingdingdang: Be bold and look!
Li Liwo: That's not right.
Jin Jinliang: Is there a key?
Li Liwo: No, that's wrong.
Nan Nandu: I checked up there, nothing.
Ningninghou: Nothing.
Ke Ke'ai: I checked behind the curtains, nothing.
He Heda: Wait, you guys didn't find a single bottle?
Ke Ke'ai: I found that one.
Jin Jinliang: I don't have any bottles here.
Dingdingdang: No bottles at my spot by the dining table.
Jin Jinliang: Come look at this.
Jin Jinliang: There really are no bottles here.
Ningninghou: Okay.
Ningninghou: Then how about this.
Ningninghou: I suspect someone saw it but won't say.
Ningninghou: So for this round,
Dingdingdang: Really?
Ningninghou: Let's switch.
Nan Nandu: Sure.
Ningninghou: How about that?
Ningninghou: I'll search here this round, okay? Super.
He Heda: Okay then, get ready and let's start.
Ke Ke'ai: You didn't search there earlier, right?
He Heda: I didn't.
Ke Ke'ai: I'll just go search there then.
Countdown begins.
Ah!
Li Liwo: Someone's here!
Li Liwo: Intruder!
Li Liwo: What the hell keeps making that noise here?